(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T08:27:20.637903",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE Midnight Mission 開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE "Midnight Mission" - Please wait for the show to start]
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE "Midnight Mission"
Please wait a moment for the show to begin.
本日の「グランド・オフィシャル・ファン・クラブ・ライブ」ファン感謝ライブ、オフィシャルミッションにおきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you for attending today's
Grand Official Fan Club Live.
大変に冷え込みまして、会場のお客さまにご案内およびご注意を申し上げます。
It is getting quite cold,
so please take precautions.
公演中の撮影、録音につきまして、固くお断りいたします。
Filming and recording are
strictly prohibited.
携帯電話は、音が鳴らないよう、電源をお切りか、マナーモードに設定をお開きいただけますようお願い申し上げます。
Please turn off your phones or
set them to manner mode.
公演中、客席前方へ駆け寄る行為、他のお客さまのご迷惑となるような行為は絶対におやめください。
Please do not run to the front
or trouble other guests.
このような行為は、大変危険ですので、固くお断りいたします。
Such behavior is dangerous
and strictly prohibited.
体調のすぐれない方、気分が悪くなられた方がいらっしゃいましたら、お近くの係員までお声がけください。
If you feel unwell or sick,
please notify a staff member.
また、定期的な換気や、適度な水分補給も行っていただきますようお願い申し上げます。
Please also ventilate regularly
and stay hydrated.
本日は、客席内に配信用のカメラを設置しております。
Streaming cameras are installed
in the audience area today.
客席内が映る可能性がございますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
You may appear on camera,
so please be aware.
演出の都合により、点灯すると、場内の非常用避難誘導灯が消灯いたします。
Emergency lights will turn off
due to production reasons.
避難が必要となった場合は、すべての避難誘導灯が速やかに点灯いたします。
They will immediately turn on
if evacuation is needed.
係員の指示があるまで慌てずに、ご自身のエリアにて待機いただきますようお願い申し上げます。
Please wait in your area
until instructed by staff.
まもなく開演いたします。ロビーにおいでのお客さまは、お早めに場内へお入りください。
The show will start soon.
Please enter the venue.
I ran from the future, I ran from the past
I ran from the future,
I ran from the past,
I ran from commitment and didn't look back
I ran from commitment
and didn't look back,
I ran from the steeple, I ran from your voice
I ran from the steeple,
I ran from your voice,
I ran to the world and I turned up the noise
I ran to the world
and I turned up the noise.
到着だ
We've arrived.
今宵の雑踏は
Tonight's hustle and bustle
まるでプログみたいなビートで舞ってる
dances to a prog-like beat.
路地裏ネオンのマーケット
Back-alley neon market,
見慣れない文字と言語をいなして
brushing off unfamiliar scripts and languages.
秘密裏にコードそっと交わして
Exchanging codes in secret,
この街が今日のターゲット
this city is today's target.
視界は悪いな逆光
Visibility is poor against the backlight,
奇奇怪怪な機構の人造ブラックホール
an artificial black hole of bizarre mechanics.
音色を仕込んだ薬莢
Cartridges loaded with tone,
あれなら二つで十分
two of those are plenty.
力んだ呼吸戻して
Regain your strained breathing,
ニキータくらい済まし顔で
with a face as composed as Nikita's.
シリンダーを出して装填 スポットライトみたいに狙いをさらって
Pull out the cylinder and load it, stealing the aim like a spotlight.
さあ始めようか
Now, shall we begin?
すべて変える4カウント
A 4-count that changes everything.
終わりのない夜をあげる合図して
Giving you an endless night, give the signal!
世界の秘密暴くよ ずっと響いているSOS
Uncovering the world's secrets, an SOS that keeps echoing.
退屈なスパイラル 3つ数えてアンロックで
A boring spiral, count to three and unlock.
反撃だ 光の海に潜って
Counterattack! Dive into the sea of light.
歌詞で繋いでいく点と線
Connecting dots and lines with lyrics.
カオティックな音に乗せて
Riding on chaotic sounds.
静寂は不穏な空気を孕んで
Silence harbors a restless air,
この部屋の闇をそっと隠している
gently concealing the darkness of this room.
右に罠 左側裏に3名
A trap on the right, left side, three in the back.
キッチュな耳鳴り
Kitsch ringing in the ears.
ソリストはもっと練習しといてって
The soloist should practice more.
狂いに狂ったチューニング
Madly, wildly out-of-tune.
さあ 終わりじゃない
Now, it's not over yet.
夜を上げる
Raising the night.
合図して
Give the signal.
世界の秘密 暴くよ
Uncovering the world's secrets.
ずっと響いているSOS
An SOS that keeps echoing.
退屈なスパイラル 3つ数えてアンロックで
A boring spiral, count to three and unlock.
反撃だ 光の海に潜って
Counterattack! Dive into the sea of light.
歌詞で繋いでいく点と線
Connecting dots and lines with lyrics.
カオティックな音に乗せて
Riding on chaotic sounds.
さあ 灰になるまで ハイになるまで
Now, until we turn to ash, until we get high.
静寂を切り裂いた号砲
The gun muzzle that tore through the silence.
幕が 開いてく
The curtain rises.
声が聞こえてる 聞こえてる
Voices are echoing, echoing...
声が聞こえてる 向こうから
...echoing from the other side.
頭に響いた あなたを辿って
Resonating in my head, following you,
今
now.
空は騒いでる 騒いでる
The sky is roaring, roaring,
未確認ヒール ワンページ
unidentified heels, page one.
アレグロを追って 駆け出して
Chasing the allegro, running out,
さあ
now—
ずっと響いている sos
An SOS keeps echoing on,
退屈なスパイラル
a tedious spiral.
3つ数えて アンロックで
Count to three and unlock,
反撃だ
time for a counterattack!
光の海に潜って
Diving into the sea of light,
歌詞で繋いでいく点と線
connecting dots and lines with lyrics,
カオティックな音に乗せて
riding on chaotic sounds.
合図して
Giving the signal!
波間に呑まれるな 呑まれるな 声を放て
Don't get swallowed by the waves, let your voice out!
あなたで光った ポイントに目掛けて
Aiming for the point where you shone bright,
今
now—
空は騒いでる 騒いでる
The sky is roaring, roaring,
流星を纏えて迎えてショーダウン
Welcoming the showdown clad in shooting stars,
逆転ロイヤルストレートフラッシュ
a reversed royal straight flush,
カオティックな音に乗せて
riding on chaotic sounds,
合図して
giving the signal!
喝采カーテンコールで
With an applause curtain call,
錆び付いている難攻不落のドアも
even the rusted, impregnable door,
アンロックで バイバイさ
unlocked, saying bye-bye!
光の海を泳いで
Swimming through the sea of light,
僕のフレーズとプレクトラム
with my phrases and plectrum,
ハイウェイで会おうぜ 走って
let's meet on the highway, run!
カオティックな音で踊って
Dancing to the chaotic sound,
さあ 灰になるまで ハイになるまで
until we turn to ash, until we get high!
ずっと響いている sos
An SOS keeps echoing on,
退屈なスパイラル
a tedious spiral.
3つ数えて アンロックで
Count to three and unlock,
反撃だ
time for a counterattack!
光の海に潜って
Diving into the sea of light,
歌詞で繋いでいく点と線
connecting dots and lines with lyrics,
カオティックな音に乗せて
riding on chaotic sounds.
合図して
Giving the signal,
世界の秘密 暴くよ
exposing the secrets of the world!
さあ 灰になるまで ハイになるまで
Until we turn to ash, until we get high!
本音も建前も 駆け引き上手な大人は 駄目だね
Adults who are good at playing games with honesty and pretense are no good, huh?
そんな言葉 信用できない
I can't trust words like that.
できない
I just can't.
便利で快適で 進化し続けるテクノロジー
Convenient and comfortable, technology that keeps evolving,
伝えて 人肌のぬくもりを
please convey the warmth of human skin.
ねえ、このままずっと 降り止まない 雨の世界だ
Hey, it's a world of rain that won't stop falling just like this.
もう悲しくない 人は慣れる生き物だから
I'm no longer sad, because humans are creatures that get used to it.
そう、白紙になった 青春の何ページ目だったっけ
Yeah, what page of youth had become a blank page?
今、君に会いたいと 涙こみ上げる
Now, tears well up wanting to see you.
踏んだり蹴ったり 注意散漫 人生の転機だ
Ups and downs, distracted, it's a turning point in life.
新しい時代を乗りこなしていくんだ
I'm going to ride out this new era.
透明で 不鮮明で 叫び声上げるマイノリティ
Transparent and unclear, minorities raising their voices in a cry,
健気に失敗しては学んでく
courageously making mistakes and learning from them.
ねえ、このままずっと 降り止まない雨の世界だ
Hey, it's a world of rain that won't stop falling just like this.
愛するしかない それしか無い 器用じゃないから
I have no choice but to love, that's all there is, because I'm not dexterous.
そう、白紙になった 青春の何ページ目だったっけ
Yeah, what page of youth had become a blank page?
忘れもの思い出せないまま
Leaving behind what I forgot without being able to remember,
忘れそう
I'm about to forget.
このまじゃ…
At this rate...
風の形見えない 見えないよ、あなたが
I can't see the shape of the wind, I can't see you,
あなただって同じ
you're the same way.
じっとなんてしてられない 動き出すよ、この身かけて
I can't just stay still, I'll set this body in motion,
こぼさないよ 泣いたってしょうがないさ
I won't spill anything, crying is no use.
ねえ、このままずっと 降り止まない雨の世界だ
Hey, it's a world of rain that won't stop falling just like this.
もう悲しくない 人は慣れる生き物だから
I'm no longer sad, because humans are creatures that get used to it.
そう、白紙になった 青春の何ページ目だったっけ
Yeah, what page of youth had become a blank page?
今、君に会いたいと 涙こらえて
Holding back my tears thinking I want to see you now.
さよならだ さよならなんだって 認めたくないけど
It's goodbye, even though I don't want to admit it's goodbye,
雨上がりの この世界が 眩しいから
because this world after the rain is so dazzling.
もう帰らない 振り返らない 思い出と共に
I won't go back, I won't look back, together with my memories,
新しい風に揺らされ そしてまた君に会いたいと願い
fanned by a new wind, and wishing once again to see you,
駆けてゆく
I'm running ahead,
running ahead.
空っぽのサイレン 乾いた施錠音
An empty siren, a dry locking sound
ガラガラスケーター 賑わえ 三点 リーダー
Rattling skaters, bustling with ellipsis
どんな言葉にも ちゃんとうねりがあった
Every single word had flaws in it
もう 何も言わずに 遊ぼう
Let's just play without saying anything anymore
どうでもいい朝に 慣れ過ぎて
Too used to mornings that don't matter
傘は持っていない 借りていた未来
I didn't have an umbrella, I was borrowing the future
返しきれず 避けきれず からから街往く 余所者
Unable to return it, unable to dodge it, barely escaping
ねえねえ 独りだ 肩触れたのは
Hey hey, I'm all alone, what brushed against my shoulder was
メイビィ、レイニー 君はとうに 居ないんだね
Maybe, rainy, you haven't been here for a long time, right?
かなしくはないよ 嬉しくもないよ
I'm not sad, nor am I happy either
メイビィ、レイニー よく晴れた 鈍色に
Maybe, rainy, in the brightly cleared dull gray
減点式の 舗装路を 染める
Dyeing the point-deduction paved road
レイニー、レイニー こんな間違うたんだね
Rainy, rainy, I made such a mistake, didn't I?
塗り潰してゆく パノラマ
The panorama that keeps being painted over
レイニー、レイニー 君は何点だったの
Rainy, rainy, what score did you get?
バイバイ バイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-bye
よく晴れた 鈍色の 正午
A brightly cleared dull gray noon
無骨な クラクション ああやって 喚いて
An unrefined car horn, shouting like that
叱り合えたら それで良かった？
Would it have been fine if we could scold each other?
泣いて 泣いて 泣いて 何が残った
Crying, crying, crying, what was left?
使い捨ての 今日を 余したくないな
I don't want to waste a disposable today
喧騒5分の 砂地公園 宇宙の裏
A five-minute commotion in the sandy park behind the universe
白い煙に 吹かれながら 呟く
Singing while being blown by white smoke
救いのない 世迷言
Hopeless mutterings
ねえねえ 独りだ 頬伝ったのは
Hey hey, I'm all alone, what traced down my cheek was
メイビィ、レイニー 走馬灯みたいな キス
Maybe, rainy, a kiss like a revolving lantern
不確かな 声に 似ている 青に
Into the blue that resembles an uncertain voice
バイバイ バイバイ しなくちゃいけないんだ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, I have to do it
ほんの微かに 雨の 随に
Just faintly, at the whim of the rain
君も往くなら 無事を祈っている
If you're going too, I pray for your safety
ねえねえ 独りだ 肩触れたのは
Hey hey, I'm all alone, what brushed against my shoulder was
メイビィ、レイニー 君はとうに 居ないんだね
Maybe, rainy, you haven't been here for a long time, right?
かなしくはないよ 嬉しくもないよ
I'm not sad, nor am I happy either
メイビィ、レイニー よく晴れた 鈍色に
Maybe, rainy, in the brightly cleared dull gray
覗き込むトワイライト
Peeking into the twilight
世界が裏返るような夢を見ていた
I was having a dream like the world was turning upside down
淀んだ薄明の向こうに
Beyond the stagnant twilight
ライトスピードで目を飛ばして
Jumping at light speed
こっちおいで追いつけないぜ
"Come over here, you can't catch up!"
セントを鳴らしてマイクチェイス
Ringing the cents and chasing the mic
バックステージのフェーズシフト
Phase shifting in the backstage
鳴り止まないトワイライトソング
The twilight song that never stops ringing out
例えば僕がこうやって呼吸をしていること
For example, the fact that I'm breathing like this
理由がなくても
Even without a reason
人混みの間で居場所を探して
Searching for a place to belong in the crowd
虚しくなったよ
It became empty
生温いベッドルームの中
Inside the lukewarm bedroom
理想とリアルその狭間
Between ideals and reality
君が置いていた時計の秒針だけ やたら響いて
Only the second hand of the clock you left behind echoes so much
覗き込むトワイライト
Peeking into the twilight
世界が裏返るような夢を見ていた
I was having a dream like the world was turning upside down
夜を待つ街灯の熱り
The heat of the streetlights waiting for the night
僕はまだ歌えない
I still cannot sing
「いつかまた会うその日まで」
"Until the day we meet again"
君が笑った
You smiled
淀んだ薄明の向こうに
Beyond the stagnant twilight
虚構の世界の果てに何かを見たくて
Wanting to see something at the end of the fictional world
歌ってきたけれど
I've been singing, but
「愛してる」のひとつも音にできなくて 虚しくなったよ
Not even a single "I love you" could be turned into sound, it became empty
繰り返す白昼月にただ寄り添っていたよ 今更
I was just clinging to a repeating daydream, now of all times
君の熱も髪の香りさえ ここには無くて
Neither your warmth nor even the scent of your hair is here
「離さないよ、最後まで」
"I won't let go, until the end"
雨ざらしの黄昏 ただ幻のように
A weathered twilight, just like an illusion,
暮れていく空 悲しみはオレンジ
The sky is darkening, sadness is orange
電線の上に並べた音符をなぞって
Tracing the notes lined up on power lines
あの日と重ねていただけ
Just overlapping with that day
覗き込むトワイライト
Peeking into the twilight
世界が裏返るような夢を見ていた
I was having a dream like the world was turning upside down
夜を待つ街灯の熱り
The heat of the streetlights waiting for the night
僕はまだ歌えない
I still cannot sing
「いつかまた会うその日まで」
"Until the day we meet again"
君が笑った
You smiled
淀んだ薄明の向こうに
Beyond the stagnant twilight
ライトスピードで目を飛ばして
Jumping at light speed
こっちおいで追いつけないぜ
"Come over here, you can't catch up!"
セントを鳴らしてマイクチェイス
Ringing the cents and chasing the mic
鳴り止まないトワイライトソング
The twilight song that never stops ringing out
Midnight Grand Orchestraでした！よろしくお願いします！
That was Midnight Grand Orchestra! Thank you very much!
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1ST LIVE Midnight Mission! 2024.2.20
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st LIVE "Midnight Mission!" Feb 20, 2024